Guide to the TV Tie-in Book Collection, 1945-1999
TV Tie-in Book Collection, 1945-1999
- Happy Days 4: Fonzie, Fonzie, Superstar by William Johnston Tempo 12414 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 17)
- Happy Days 5: The Fonz & La Zonga by William Johnston Tempo 12607 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 17)
- Happy Days 6: The Bike Tycoon by William Johnston Tempo 12609 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 17)
- Happy Days 6: The Bike Tycoon by William Johnston c 1976 (Variant Cover) (Box 17)
- Happy Days 7: Dear Fonzie by William Johnston Tempo 12946 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 17)
- Happy Days 8: Fonzie Goes to College by William Johnston Tempo 14034 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 17)
- Happy Days Box Set: Happy Days 1-6 by William Johnston Tempo (Box 17)
- The Official Fonzie Scrapbook by Ben Davidson Tempo 14044 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 17)
- Hollywood's Newest Superstar: Henry Winkler by Suzanne Munshower Berkley Z3231 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 17)
- The Fonze: The Henry Winkler Story by Charles E. Pike Pocket 80746 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 17)
- The Truth About Fonzie by Peggy Herz Scholastic Book Services TK3571 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 18)
- fonzie! by Martin A. Grove Zebra 89083-228 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 18)
- The Shaun Cassidy Scrapbook by Connie Berman Tempo 14738 ca. 1978 (1st) (Box 18)
- Harry O #1 by Lee Hays Popular Library 00269 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 18)
- Harry O #2: The High Cost of Living by Lee Hays Popular Library 00337 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 18)
- Have Gun, Will Travel by Noel Loomis Dell First Edition B156 ca. 1960 (1st) (Box 18)
- Have Gun, Will Travel: A Man Called Paladin by Frank C. Robertson Macfadden 60-191 ca. 1963 (1st: 1964) (Box 18)
- Hawaii Five-O by Michael Avallone Signet P3622 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 18)
- Hawaii Five-O by Michael Avallone Signet T5817 ca. 1968 (4th: 1970) (Variant Cover) (Box 18)
- Hawaii Five-O #2: Terror in the Sun by Michael Avallone Signet P3994 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 18)
- Hawaii Five-O #2: Terror in the Sun by Michael Avallone Signet T5818 ca. 1969 (3rd: 1970) (Variant Cover) (Box 18)
- Hawaii Five-O: The Angry Battalion by Herbert Harris Star Book ca. 1972 (Box 18)
- Hawaiian Eye by Frank Castle Dell First Edition K112 ca. 1962 (1st) (Box 18)
- Hawk by Richard Hardwick Belmont B50-741 ca. 1966 (1st) (Box 18)
- All Hazel by Ted Key Bantam A2411 ca. 1958 (1st: 1962) (Box 18)
- All Hazel by Ted Key Bantam J2991 ca. 1958 (2nd: 1965) (Box 18)
- Hazel Time by Ted Key Bantam J2990 ca. 1962 (1st: 1965) (Box 18)
- Life With Hazel by Ted Key Bantam F3325 ca. 1965 (1st: 1967) (Box 18)
- Head of the Class by Susan Beth Pfeffer Bantam 28190 ca. 1989 (1st) (Box 18)
- Hec Ramsey by Dean Owen [Dudley Dean McGaughy] Award AN1169 ca. 1973 (1st) (Box 18)
- Hec Ramsey #2: The Hunted by Joe Millard Award AN1232 ca. 1974 (1st) (Box 18)
- Here Comes the Brides by Chris Stratton [Richard Hubbard] Curtis 06062 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 18)
- The High Chaparral: Coyote Gold by Ed Friend [Richard Wormser] Tempo 05302 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 18)
- The High Chaparral: Hell and High Water by Wayne Sottona Tempo 05319 ca. 1968 (1st: 1969) (Box 18)
- Zingers From The Hollywood Squares by Gail Sicilia, ed. Popular Library 00221 ca. 1974 (1st) (Box 18)
- More Zingers From The Hollywood Squares by Gail Sicilia, ed. Popular Library 04113 ca. 1978 (1st) (Box 18)
- This Girl for Hire by G.G. Fickling [Skip and Gloria Fickling] Pyramid R-1151 ca. 1957 (4th: 1965) (Box 18)
- This Girl for Hire by G.G. Fickling Pyramid R-1360 ca. 1957 (5th: 1965) (Variant Cover) (Box 18)
- A Gun for Honey by G.G. Fickling Pyramid R-1167 ca. 1958 (2nd: 1965) (Box 18)
- A Gun for Honey by G.G. Fickling Pyramid R-1358 ca. 1958 (3rd: 1965) (Variant Cover) (Box 18)
- Honey in the Flesh by G.G. Fickling Pyramid R-1179 ca. 1959 (2nd: 1965) (Box 18)
- Honey in the Flesh by G.G. Fickling Pyramid R-1359 ca. 1959 (3rd: 1965) (Variant Cover) (Box 18)
- Girl on the Prowl by G.G. Fickling Pyramid R-1339 ca. 1959 (2nd: 1965) (Box 18)
- Blood and Honey by G.G. Fickling Pyramid R-1340 ca. 1961 (2nd: 1965) (Box 18)
- Dig a Dead Doll by G.G. Fickling Pyramid R-1355 ca. 1960 (2nd: 1965) (Box 18)
- Girl on the Loose by G.G. Fickling Pyramid R-1356 ca. 1958 (2nd: 1965) (Box 19)
- Kiss for a Killer by G.G. Fickling Pyramid R-1357 ca. 1960 (2nd: 1965) (Box 19)
- Kiss for a Killer by G.G. Fickling Pyramid G520 ca. 1960 (Box 19)
- Bombshell by G.G. Fickling Pyramid R-1106 ca. 1964 (1st) (Box 19)
- Bombshell by G.G. Fickling Pyramid R-1354 ca. 1964 (2nd: 1965) (Box 19)
- Honey on Her Tail by G.G. Fickling Pyramid T2410 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 19)
- Stiff as a Broad by G.G. Fickling Pyramid T2494 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 19)
- How the West Was Won by Lou Cameron Ballantine 27401 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 19)
- How the West Was Won, by Louis L'Amour Bantam F2548 ca. 1962 (Box 19)
- I Spy by John Tiger [Walter Wagner] Popular Library SP400 ca. 1965 (1st) (Box 19)
- I Spy #2: Masterstroke by John Tiger [Walter Wagner] Popular Library 60-2127 ca. 1966 (1st) (Box 19)
- I Spy #3: Superkill by John Tiger [Walter Wagner] Popular Library 60-2157 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 19)
- I Spy #4: Wipeout by John Tiger [Walter Wagner] Popular Library 60-2180 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 19)
- I Spy #5: Countertrap by John Tiger [Walter Wagner] Popular Library 60-2206 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 19)
- I Spy #6: Doomdate by John Tiger [Walter Wagner] Popular Library 60-2237 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 19)
- I Spy #7: Death-Twist by John Tiger [Walter Wagner] Popular Library 60-2311 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 19)
- The Immortal by James E. Gunn Bantam S5924 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 19)
- In Search of Lost Civilizations (#1) by Alan Landsburg Bantam 10582 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 19)
- In Search of Extraterrestrials (#2) by Alan Landsburg Bantam 10722 ca. 1976 (1st: 1977) (Box 19)
- In Search of Magic and Witchcraft (#3) by Alan Landsburg Bantam 10851 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 19)
- In Search of Strange Phenomena (#4) by Alan Landsburg Bantam 10855 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 19)
- In Search of Myths and Monsters by Alan Landsburg Bantam 11137 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 19)
- In Search of Missing Persons by Alan Landsburg Bantam 11459 ca. 1978 (1st) (Box 19)
- Stan Lee Presents The Incredible Hulk by Stan Lee Pocket 81446 ca. 1978 (1st) (Box 19)
- Stan Lee Presents The Incredible Hulk #2 by Stan Lee Pocket 82559 ca. 1978 (1st: 1979) (Box 19)
- The Incredible Hulk in Stalker From the Stars by Len Wein, Marv Wolfman and "Joseph Silva" [Ron Goulart] Pocket 82084 ca. 1978 (1st) (Box 19)
- The Incredible Hulk in Cry of the Beast by Richard S. Meyers Pocket 82085 ca. 1979 (1st) (Box 19)
- The Hulk and Spider-Man in Murdermoon by Paul Kupperberg Pocket 82094 ca. 1979 (1st) (Box 19)
- Stan Lee Presents The Incredible Hulk: A Video Novel by Roy Thomas, ed. Pocket 82827 ca. 1979 (1st) (Box 20)
- The Incredible Hulk by Stan Lee and Larry Lieber Tempo 17179 ca. 1980 (1st) (Box 20)
- The Incredible Hulk Volume 2 by Stan Lee and Larry Lieber Tempo 17314 ca. 1981 (1st) (Box 20)
- The Invaders #1 by Keith Laumer Pyramid R-1664 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 20)
- The Invaders #2: Enemies From Beyond by Keith Laumer Pyramid X-1689 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 20)
- The Invaders #3: Army of the Undead by Rafe Bernard Pyramid R-1711 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 20)
- The Invisible Man by Michael Jahn Fawcett Gold Medal P3460 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 20)
- The Iron Horse by William Johnston Popular Library 60-2156 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 20)
- Ironside by Jim Thompson Popular Library 60-2244 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 20)
- It Takes a Thief #1: The Devil in Davos by Gil Brewer Ace 37598 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 20)
- It Takes a Thief #2: Mediterranean Caper by Gil Brewer Ace 37599 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 20)
- It Takes a Thief #3: Appointment in Cairo by Gil Brewer Ace 37600 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 20)
- It's Your Move by William Rotsler Archway 54716 ca. 1984 (1st) (Box 20)
- Charley Weaver's Letters from Mamma by Cliff Arquette Dell D347 ca. 1959 (1st: 1960) (Box 20)
- Yours Truly, Hugh Downs by Hugh Downs Avon F-106 ca. 1960 (1st) (Box 20)
- I Kid You Not by Jack Paar Cardinal GC-103 ca. 1959,60 (1st: 1961) (Box 20)
- My Saber is Bent by Jack Paar Cardinal GC-148 ca. 1961 (1st: 1962) (Box 20)
- The Real Jack Paar by George Johnson Gold Medal s1263 ca. 1962 (1st) (Box 20)
- What is Jack Paar Really Like? by William H.A. Carr Lancer 70-005 ca. 1962 (1st) (Box 20)
- James at 15 by April Smith Dell 14389 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 20)
- James at 15 by April Smith Dell 94389 ca. 1977 (1st Laurelleaf: 1980) (Variant Cover) (Box 20)
- James at 15: Friends by April Smith Dell 12666 ca. 1978 (1st) (Box 20)
- James at 15: Friends by April Smith Dell 92666 ca. 1978 (1st Laurelleaf: 1980) (Variant Cover) (Box 20)
- Code Name: Jericho - Operation Goldkill by Bruce Cassiday Award A211FK ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 20)
- Joanie Loves Chachi by Roger Elwood Weekly Reader F536 ca. 1982 (1st) (Box 20)
- Johnny Staccato by Frank Boyd [Frank Kane] Gold Medal 980 ca. 1960 (1st) (Box 20)
- Judd for the Defense by Lawrence Louis Goldman Paperback Library 53-625 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 20)
- Judd for the Defense #2: The Secret Listeners by Lawrence Louis Goldman Paperback Library 53-721 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 20)
- Knight Rider by Glen A. Larson and Roger Hill Pinnacle 42170 ca. 1983 (1st) (Box 20)
- Knight Rider #2: Trust Doesn't Rust by Glen A. Larson and Roger Hill Pinnacle 42181 ca. 1984 (1st) (Box 20)
- Knight Rider #3: Hearts of Stone by Glen A. Larson and Roger Hill Pinnacle 42182 ca. 1984 (1st) (Box 21)
- Knots Landing #1: Secrets of Knots Landing by Mary Ann Cooper Pioneer 61 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 21)
- Knots Landing #2: Uncharted Love by Samantha Phillips [Sandi Gelles-Cole] Pioneer 62 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 21)
- Knots Landing #3: Love Unbound by Anne Cavaliere Pioneer 63 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 21)
- Knots Landing #4: Misguided Hearts by Scott Cunningham Pioneer 64 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 21)
- Knots Landing #5: Mothers and Daughters by Samantha Phillips [Sandi Gelles-Cole] Pioneer 65 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 21)
- Knots Landing #6: Starting Over by Brian Wolff Pioneer 66 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 21)
- Knots Landing #7: Tell Me No Lies by Scott Cunningham Pioneer 67 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 21)
- Knots Landing #8: Once in a Lifetime by Victoria Dann Pioneer 68 ca. 1986 (1st) (Box 21)
- Knots Landing #9: A House Divided by Anne Cavaliere Pioneer 69 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 21)
- Knots Landing #10: Family Affairs by Marcia Lawrence Pioneer 70 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 21)
- Knots Landing #11: A Second Chance by Amanda Preble Pioneer 200 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 21)
- Knots Landing #13: Dangerous Games by D.L. Adler Pioneer 202 ca. 1987 (1st) (Box 21)
- Kojak #1: Siege by Victor B. Miller Pocket 78487 ca. 1974 (1st) (Box 21)
- Kojak #2: Requiem for a Cop by Victor B. Miller Pocket 78488 ca. 1974 (1st) (Box 21)
- Kojak #3: Girl in the River by Victor B. Miller Pocket 78817 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 21)
- Kojak #4: Therapy in Dynamite by Victor B. Miller Pocket 78865 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 21)
- Kojak #5: Death Is Not a Passing Grade by Victor B. Miller Pocket 78912 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 21)
- Kojak #6: A Very Deadly Game by Victor B. Miller Pocket 78960 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 21)
- Kojak #7: Take-over by Victor B. Miller Pocket 78996 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 21)
- Kojak #7: Take-over by Victor B. Miller Star Original ca. 1976 (Box 21)
- Kojak #8: Gun Business by Victor B. Miller Pocket 78998 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 21)
- Kojak #9: The Trade-off by Victor B. Miller Pocket 80045 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 21)
- Kojak in San Francisco by Thom Racina Berkley Z3237 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 21)
- Telly Savalas: TV's Golden Greek by Marsha Daly Berkley Z3021 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 21)
- Patterns by Rod Sterling Bantam F1832 ca. 1955+ (1st: 1958) (Box 21)
- Kung Fu #1: The Way of the Tiger, the Sign of the Dragon by Howard Lee [Barry N. Malzberg] Warner 76-464 ca. 1973 (1st) (Box 21)
- Kung Fu #2: Chains by Howard Lee [Ron Goulart] Warner 76-465 ca. 1973 (1st) (Box 21)
- Kung Fu #3: Superstitions by Howard Lee [Ron Goulart] Warner 76-466 ca. 1973 (1st) (Box 21)
- Kung Fu #4: A Praying Mantis Kills by Howard Lee [Lou Cameron] Warner 76-467 ca. 1974 (1st) (Box 22)
- Kung Fu: The Peaceful Way by Richard Robinson Pyramid 03315 ca. 1974 (1st) (Box 22)
- Lancer by Paul W. Fairman Popular Library 60-2349 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 22)
- Land of the Giants by Murray Leinster [Will F. Jenkins] Pyramid X-1846 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 22)
- Land of the Giants #2: The Hot Spot by Murray Leinster [Will F. Jenkins] Pyramid X-1921 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 22)
- Land of the Giants #3: Unknown Danger by Murray Leinster [Will F. Jenkins] Pyramid X-2105 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 22)
- Last of the Summer Wine by Roy Clarke Coronet 18994 ca. 1974 (1st) (Box 22)
- Rowan & Martin's Laugh-In #1 by Morgul the Friendly Drelb Signet T3844 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 22)
- Rowan & Martin's Laugh-In #2: Mod, Mod World by Roy Doty Signet T3845 ca. 1968,69 (1st: 1969) (Box 22)
- Rowan & Martin's Laugh-In #3: Inside Laugh-In by James E. Brodhead Signet T4059 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 22)
- Rowan & Martin's Laugh-In #4: JoAnne Worley's Chicken Joke Book by JoAnne Worley with Dick Matthews Signet T4060 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 22)
- Here Come the Judge! by Dewey "Pigmeat" Markham with Bill Levinson Popular Library 60-8080 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 22)
- Laverne and Shirley #1: Teamwork by Con Steffanson [Ron Goulart] Warner 88-294 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 22)
- Laverne and Shirley #2: East Money by Con Steffanson [Ron Goulart] Warner 88-295 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 22)
- Laverne and Shirley #3: Gold Rush by Con Steffanson [Ron Goulart] Warner 88-296 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 22)
- The Law by Bill S. Ballinger Warner 76920 ca. 1975 (Box 22)
- Leave it to Beaver by Beverly Cleary Berkley Medallion G406 ca. 1960 (1st) (Box 22)
- Leave it to Beaver by Beverly Cleary Berkley Highland F1331 ca. 1960 (3rd: 1966) (Variant Cover) (Box 22)
- Here's Beaver by Beverly Cleary Berkley Medallion G497 ca. 1961 (1st) (Box 22)
- Here's Beaver by Beverly Cleary Berkley Highland F1332 ca. 1961 (2nd: 1966) (Box 22)
- Beaver and Wally by Beverly Cleary Berkley Medallion G557 ca. 1961 (1st) (Box 22)
- Let's Make a Deal: Emcee Monty Hall by Monte Hall and Bill Libby Ballantine 24370 ca. 1973 (1st: 1975) (Box 22)
- The Life and Times of Grizzly Adams by Charles E. Selier, Jr. Schick Sunn 917215 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 22)
- The Lineup by Frank Kane Dell First Edition B125 ca. 1959 (1st) (Box 22)
- Little House on the Prairie by Laura Ingalls Wilder Perennial Library P357 ca. 1935 (1st: 1975) (Box 22)
- Debbie Preston Teenage Reporter in the Michael Gray Hawaiian Mystery by James Carter Tiger Beat XQ2024 ca. 1973 (1st: 1971) (Box 22)
- Longstreet: The Last Express by Baynard Kendrick Lancer 74779 ca. 1937 (1st: 1971) (Box 22)
- Longstreet: Reservations For Death by Baynard Kendrick Lancer 74784 ca. 1956,57 (1st: 1971) (Box 22)
- Longstreet: Blind Man's Bluff by Baynard Kendrick Lancer 74788 ca. 1943 (1st: 1971) (Box 22)
- Longstreet: Out of Control by Baynard Kendrick Lancer 75287 ca. 1945 (1st: 1972) (Box 22)
- Lost in Space by Dave Van Arnam and "Ron Archer" [Ted White] Pyramid X-1679 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 22)
- Love American Style by Paul Fairman Pinnacle P047-N ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 22)
- Love American Style, 2 by Paul Fairman Pinnacle P081-N ca. 1972 (1st) (Box 22)
- The Love Boats by Jereldine Saunders Pinnacle 240698 ca. 1974 (2nd: 1976) (Box 23)
- The Love Boats by Jereldine Saunders Pinnacle 230698 ca. 1974 (Variant Cover) (Box 23)
- Love of Life by Margaret Manners Dell First Edition B183 ca. 1961 (1st) (Box 23)
- Love of Life: The Perilous Summer by Joan Hughes Pocket 75445 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 23)
- Lucan by C.K. Chandler Ballantine 27402 ca. 1977 (1st: 1978) (Box 23)
- Lucas Tanner: A Question of Guilt by Richard Posner Pyramid V3777 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 23)
- Lucas Tanner #2: A Matter of Love by Richard Posner Pyramid V3928 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 23)
- Lucas Tanner #3: For Her to Decide by Richard Posner Pyramid V4042 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 23)
- MaCloud #1 by Collin Wilcox Award AN1203 ca. 1973 (1st) (Box 23)
- MaCloud #2: The New Mexico Connection by Collin Wilcox Award AN1259 ca. 1974 (1st) (Box 23)
- MaCloud #3: The Killing by David Wilson Award AN1281 ca. 1974 (1st) (Box 23)
- MaCloud #4: The Corpse-Maker by David Wilson Award AN1365 ca. 1974 (1st) (Box 23)
- MaCloud #5: A Dangerous Place to Die by David Wilson Award AN1368 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 23)
- MaCloud #6: Park Avenue Executioner by David Wilson Award AQ1463 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 23)
- McCoy by Sam Stewart [Linda Stewart] Dell 05293 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 23)
- Mackenzie's Raiders: The Mackenzie Raid by Colonel Red Reeder Ballantine 110 ca. 1955 (Box 23)
- Mackenzie's Raiders: The Mackenzie Raid by Colonel Red Reeder Ballantine 460K ca. 1955 (unsp: 1960) (Variant Cover) (Box 23)
- M Squad: The Case of the Chicago Cop-Killer by David Saunders [Dan Sontup] Belmont 91-254 ca. 1962 (1st) (Box 23)
- M*A*S*H by Richard Hooker Pocket 77232 ca. 1968 (16th: 1973) (Box 23)
- M*A*S*H by Richard Hooker Pocket 77232 ca. 1968 (Variant Cover) (Box 23)
- M*A*S*H by Richard Hooker Pocket 75453 ca. 1968 (Variant Cover) (Box 23)
- M*A*S*H Goes to Maine by Richard Hooker Pocket 78815 ca. 1971 (10th: 1975) (Box 23)
- M*A*S*H Goes to New Orleans by Richard Hooker and William E. Butterworth Pocket 78490 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 23)
- M*A*S*H Goes to Paris by Richard Hooker and William E. Butterworth Pocket 78491 ca. 1974 (1st: 1975) (Box 23)
- M*A*S*H Goes to London by Richard Hooker and William E. Butterworth Pocket 78941 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 23)
- M*A*S*H Goes to Morocco by Richard Hooker and William E. Butterworth Pocket 80264 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 23)
- M*A*S*H Goes to Las Vegas by Richard Hooker and William E. Butterworth Pocket 80265 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 23)
- M*A*S*H Goes to Hollywood by Richard Hooker and William E. Butterworth Pocket 80408 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 23)
- M*A*S*H Goes to Vienna by Richard Hooker and William E. Butterworth Pocket 80458 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 24)
- M*A*S*H Goes to Miami by Richard Hooker and William E. Butterworth Pocket 80705 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 24)
- M*A*S*H Goes to San Francisco by Richard Hooker and William E. Butterworth Pocket 80786 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 24)
- M*A*S*H Goes to Texas by Richard Hooker and William E. Butterworth Pocket 80892 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 24)
- M*A*S*H Goes to Montreal by Richard Hooker and William E. Butterworth Pocket 80910 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 24)
- M*A*S*H Goes to Moscow by Richard Hooker and William E. Butterworth Pocket 80911 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 24)
- M*A*S*H Mania by Richard Hooker Pocket 82178 ca. 1977 (1st: 1979) (Box 24)
- All About "M*A*S*H" by Peggy Herz Scholastic Book Services TK3237 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 24)
- M*A*S*H: The Official 4077 Quiz Manual by Paul Bertling Signet AE4135 ca. 1984 (1st: 1986) (Box 24)
- M*A*S*H Trivia: The Unofficial Quiz Book by George St. John Warner 32000 ca. 1983 (1st) (Box 24)
- Tom Selleck: An Unauthorized Biography by Jason Bonderoff Signet AE2063 ca. 1983 (1st) (Box 24)
- Mama's Bank Account by Kathryn Forbes Bantam 1513 ca. 1943 (2nd: 1956) (Box 24)
- Mama's Bank Account by Kathryn Forbes Bantam 135 ca. 1943 (Variant Cover) (Box 24)
- Man From Atlantis #1 by Richard Woodley Dell 15368 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 24)
- Man From Atlantis #2: Death Scouts by Richard Woodley Dell 15369 ca. 1977 (1st) (Box 24)
- Man From Atlantis #3: Killer Spores by Richard Woodley Dell 15926 ca. 1978 (1st) (Box 24)
- Man From Atlantis #4: Ark of Doom by Richard Woodley Dell 15927 ca. 1978 (1st) (Box 24)
- The Man From U.N.C.L.E. by Michael Avallone Ace G-553 ca. 1965 (1st) (Box 24)
- The Man From U.N.C.L.E. #2: The Doomsday Affair by Harry Whittington Ace G-560 ca. 1965 (1st) (Box 24)
- The Man From U.N.C.L.E. #3: The Copenhagen Affair by John Oram [John Oram Thomas] Ace G-564 ca. 1965 (1st) (Box 24)
- The Man From U.N.C.L.E. #4: The Dagger Affair by David McDaniel Ace G-571 ca. 1965 (1st: 1966) (Box 24)
- The Man From U.N.C.L.E. #5: The Mad Scientist Affair by John T. Phillifent Ace G-581 ca. 1966 (1st) (Box 24)
- The Man From U.N.C.L.E. #6: The Vampire Affair by David McDaniel Ace G-590 ca. 1966 (1st) (Box 24)
- The Man From U.N.C.L.E. #7: The Radioactive Camel Affair by Peter Leslie Ace G-600 ca. 1966 (1st) (Box 24)
- The Man From U.N.C.L.E. #8: The Monster Wheel Affair by David McDaniel Ace G-613 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 24)
- The Man From U.N.C.L.E. #9: Driving Dames Affair by Peter Leslie Ace G-617 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 24)
- The Man From U.N.C.L.E. #10: The Assassination Affair by J. Hunter Holly [Joan Carol Holly] Ace G-636 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 24)
- The Man From U.N.C.L.E. #11: The Invisibility Affair by Thomas Stratton [Gene DeWeese and Robert Coulson] Ace G-645 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 24)
- The Man From U.N.C.L.E. #12: The Mid-Twisters Affair by Thomas Stratton [Gene DeWeese and Robert Coulson] Ace G-663 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 24)
- The Man From U.N.C.L.E. #13: The Rainbow Affair by David McDaniel Ace G-670 ca. 1967 (1st) (Box 24)
- The Man From U.N.C.L.E. #14: The Cross of Gold Affair by Fredric Davies [Ron Ellik and Fredricc Langley] Ace G-689 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 25)
- The Man From U.N.C.L.E. #15: The Utopia Affair by David McDaniel Ace G-729 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 25)
- The Man From U.N.C.L.E. #16: The Splintered Sunglasses Affair by Peter Leslie Ace G-752 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 25)
- The Man From U.N.C.L.E. #17: The Hollow Crown Affair by David McDaniel Ace 51700 ca. 1969 (1st) (Box 25)
- The Man From U.N.C.L.E. #18: The Unfair Fare Affair by Peter Leslie Ace 51701 ca. 1968 (1st: 1969) (Box 25)
- The Man From U.N.C.L.E. #19: The Power Cube Affair by John T. Phillifent Ace 51702 ca. 1968 (1st: 1969) (Box 25)
- The Man From U.N.C.L.E. #20: The Corfu Affair by John T. Phillifent Ace 51703 ca. 1967 (1st: 1970) (Box 25)
- The Man From U.N.C.L.E. #21: The Thinking Machine Affair by Joel Berard Ace 51704 ca. 1967 (1st: 1970) (Box 25)
- The Man From U.N.C.L.E. #22: The Stone-Cold Dead in the Market Affair by John Oram [John Oram Thomas] Ace 51705 ca. 1966 (1st: 1971) (Box 25)
- The Man From U.N.C.L.E. #23: The Finger in the Sky Affair by Peter Leslie Ace 51706 ca. 1966 (1st: 1971) (Box 25)
- The Man From U.N.C.L.E.'s ABC of Espionage by John Hill Signet D3045 ca. 1966 (1st) (Box 25)
- Mannix by Michael Avallone Popular Library 60-2256 ca. 1968 (1st) (Box 25)
- Mannix #1: The Faces of Murder by J.T. MacCargo Belmont Tower 50793 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 25)
- Mannix #2: A Fine Day For Dying by J.T. MacCargo [Pete Rabe] Belmont Tower 50823 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 25)
- Mannix #3: A Walk on the Blind Side by J.T. MacCargo Belmont Tower 50825 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 25)
- Mannix #4: Round Trip to Nowhere by J.T. MacCargo [Pete Rabe] Belmont Tower 50834 ca. 1975 (1st) (Box 25)
- The Many Loves of Dobie Gillis by Max Shulman Bantam F2041 ca. 1945+ (1st: 1960) (Box 25)
- Marcus Welby, M.D.: Rock a Cradle Empty by Bruce Cassiday Ace 51938 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 25)
- Marcus Welby, M.D. #2: The Acid Test by Bruce Cassiday Ace 51939 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 25)
- Marcus Welby, M.D. #3: The Fire's Center by Bruce Cassiday Ace 51941 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 25)
- Markham: The Case of the Pornographic Photos by Lawrence Block Belmont 236 ca. 1961 (1st) (Box 25)
- Louise Lasser, Louise Lasser by Kate Brosnan Belmont Tower 50992 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 25)
- The Mary Hartman Story by Daniel Lockwood Bolder 9098 ca. 1976 (1st) (Box 25)
- The Real Mary Tyler Moore by Chris Bryars Pinnacle 230988 ca. 1976 (1st: 1977) (Box 25)
- Matt Lincoln #1: The Revolutionist by Ed Garth [William Johnston] Lancer 73201 ca. 1970 (1st) (Box 25)
- Matt Lincoln #2: The Hostage by Ed Garth [William Johnston] Lancer 73211 ca. 1971 (1st) (Box 25)
- Poker According to Maverick [BC: Royal Flush] by J. Hoyt Cummings Dell First Edition B142 ca. 1959 (1st) (Box 25)
- Poker According to Maverick [BC: Ad for Kaiser Aluminum] by J. Hoyt Cummings Dell First Edition B142 ca. 1959 (1st) (Box 25)
- Poker According to Maverick [BC: Ad for Jeep Vehicles] by J. Hoyt Cummings Dell First Edition B142 ca. 1959 (1st) (Box 25)
- Poker According to Maverick [BC: Ad for Drackett Cleaning Products] by J. Hoyt Cummings Dell First Edition B142 ca. 1959 (1st) (Box 25)